dasolo.info 2014-08-26

# Privacy-Policy » Da Solo Download

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which dasolo.info collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the [www.dasolo.info](http://www.generateprivacypolicy.com/account/policies/edit/www.dasolo.info) website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by dasolo.info.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We do not collect any non-personal identification information about Users. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our site does not use "cookies" to enhance User experience. 

**How we use collected information**

dasolo.info may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _\- To login our Site_  

  * _\- To send periodic emails_  
We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. 

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Our Site is in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. 

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

**DMCA Policy**  
dasolo.info is in compliance with 17 U.S.C. § 512 and the Digital Millennium Copyright Act ("DMCA"). It is our policy to respond to any infringement notices and take appropriate actions under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act ("DMCA") and other applicable intellectual property laws.

If your copyrighted material has been posted on dasolo.info or if links to your copyrighted material are returned through our search engine and you want this material removed, you must provide a written communication that details the information listed in the following section. Please be aware that you will be liable for damages (including costs and attorneys' fees) if you misrepresent information listed on our site that is infringing on your copyrights. We suggest that you first contact an attorney for legal assistance on this matter.

The following elements must be included in your copyright infringement claim:

    Provide evidence of the authorized person to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.  
    Provide sufficient contact information so that we may contact you. You must also include a valid email address.  
    You must identify in sufficient detail the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed and including at least one search term under which the material appears in dasolo.info' search results.  
    A statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.  
    A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.  
    Must be signed by the authorized person to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly being infringed.

Send the written infringement notice to the following email address: dasolo@dasolo.info  
Only the notification sended to this email will be read because the other emails are automatic.

Please allow 1-5 business days for an email response. Note that emailing your complaint to other parties such as our Internet Service Provider will not expedite your request and may result in a delayed response due the complaint not properly being filed.

 **statement**  
dasolo.info does not host any streaming video content or materials of any kind.  
All that is visible on this site is connected to materila that was uploaded to video hosting sites online, such as Veoh.com, Megavideo.com, Youtube.com, etc.. Users of the respective video hosting sites have agreed to the terms of access, which forces them not to upload illegal content  
Clicking on a link on this dasolo.info, look up material on other sites, and we take no responsibility for any material on other websites. We do not charge any videos, I do not know by whom or from where the videos are. Our descriptions also do not promote or encourage illegal behavior of any kind.  
The articles submitted by users are not moderated if not the form of publication, and in any case the user is responsible for material published.  
To report abuse in relation to content, files or the site please email dasolo@dasolo.info with a brief summary/description of the issue at hand. Abusive files will be deleted expeditiously.  
dasolo@dasolo.info

**Changes to this privacy policy**

dasolo.info has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
dasolo.info  
dasolo@dasolo.info  
This document was last updated on May 19, 2013
